I'm freezing.
Death adding a scarf to my ensemble tomorrow.
Evenings have been pretty nippy lately, haven't they?
Um, hey.
Uh, yourself.
Listen, you!
If you think I'm going to let you steal my boyfriend, think again.
I just said hey and now I'm a boyfriend.
You do much weirder stuff than say hey and you know it.
I've seen how dodgy-feely you do get.
Oh, sorry about that.
I mean, we are closer.
Way more than we used to be, but that's it.
All we are is friends.
I started out as Miyamoto's friend, too, you know.
So exactly how close do you intend to get to him?
You're that threatened by me?
Shindo's ten times worse.
No!
I didn't realize.
Do you love Shindo more than me?
Absolutely not!
Then what did you mean?
What makes Shindo such a threat to me?
Well, threat might be too strong of a word,
but I have seen him go over to Miyamura's place
to pick up a change of clothes in the past.
Look, he invites himself, okay?
Not my fault.
Hmm.
A wild Shindo appears!
You guys having a block party over here or what?
Mind if I join?
Looks like fun.
Random question.
But are you and Chika fairly close?
Eh, studying for exams has been eating up all her time,
so not lately, no.
I've spent plenty of sleepless nights at Miyamura's, though,
so don't feel too bad for me.
You hungry?
Let's grab a burger.
Yeah, you're always trying to have a cow anyway,
so why not eat one instead?
I'm so lost right now,
but a burger actually does sound good.
Ooh, did that coupon expire yet?
Uh, yeah, it did.
Miyamura, let's make something clear.
Okay?
Girls are the least of my concerns.
Guys, on the other hand,
I see them taking you so easily,
and I just can't.
You see them taking me how?
Promise me one thing.
If you fall for someone else,
it better be a girl.
Can you do that for me?
Sure.
Consider it done.
So you all need to stay out of my bubble.
From now on,
I need you to keep your distance.
What about when you gotta go,
like, to the toilet?
I won't go in public!
I'll hold it!
The things you do for love,
have fun with that.
No, I'm your host.
All right.
You can just consider it as stupid.
We'll be right back.
It's my sister's.
Still...
Speaking of, here she is.
Akana Yanagi, pleased to make your acquaintance.
Good grief.
Didn't think Yuki was capable of making friends as hot as you.
You dating and keeping it on the DL?
Wish I could say we were, but she turned me down.
Yeah, figures.
Someone like you wouldn't even...
No, back up!
She turned you down?
You don't have to keep talking, you know?
That can't be accurate, can it?
I assure you, it is.
She's way out of my league.
My sister?
We're still talking about the same person, right?
I know exactly what you're thinking, so you can stop looking at me like that, okay?
Huh?
Please excuse her for the time being.
Totally fine.
I'm just happy I ran into you.
Talking with you outside of school is kind of like a dream come true.
Oh, I shouldn't have said that.
Ishikawa would get upset if he knew.
You're sweet, which is why I don't think he'd mind at all.
I know for a fact, Toadu wouldn't be upset.
But I keep on lying.
Guess what?
I heard they're dating now.
Aw, it makes sense, though.
Think about it.
They're constantly together.
Oh, for sure.
They make such a good couple.
I know that we've got Kono completely fooled.
Fooled how?
She thinks I'm dating Toadu, right?
She actually fell for a charade.
I have no clue.
She hasn't mentioned it to me.
She did.
Because she asked about it yesterday.
And I didn't deny it.
I said the rumors were true.
Why did I say that, though?
What part of me thought I would be okay to light her face?
And you're telling me this because you're hoping I'll explain to Sakura what's really going on.
Mm-hmm.
Remy doesn't have to explain, you know.
If you really do have a crush on him, I'll stay quiet.
That's not fair.
I'm failing to see how.
What's unfair is you, Yuki.
She's right.
I'm not being considerate of Kono.
At all.
I was well aware lying would hurt her.
But I did it anyway.
I'm terrible.
As she was running away, I saw her lips trembling so fast.
I didn't know they could do that.
All right, then.
It's about time I started telling the truth.
So here it is.
I see.
Thanks for being honest, Yuki.
I know this won't last forever.
I knew it from the very beginning.
Toru would have to have romantic feelings for me.
And he doesn't.
The first day we pretended to be dating should have also been the last.
But he still holds my hand.
He's so nice to me, even when I don't deserve it.
We might have to keep this up, just in case he catches on.
Are you okay with that?
Yeah, sure.
It's fine.
Being found out didn't really bother me.
I think what I wanted was for our lie to become something real.
But, even if it did, it would always be tainted.
Ah, Yuki was absent yet again.
Jeez, how many days is that?
Three, I think.
Or four.
However long it's been, I don't like it one bit.
I wonder if maybe she's sick.
Being sick wouldn't stop her from returning my texts, though.
Have you heard from her?
Toru?
Oh, sorry.
What's up?
Come back to Earth, please.
Yuki's more important than your phone.
But since you have it out, can you see if she texted you?
Already checked.
She's not talking to me, either.
Maybe it's family drama or something.
Who knows?
Oh, we should probably tell her that test is going to cover a whole bunch of different stuff now.
Ah, good idea.
Try and tell her in person, so you can watch the tantrum she throws.
Hey, she's more mature than that.
Sure hope she comes tomorrow.
Yeah.
Come on.
I don't know what's wrong, but you need to go back to school.
Does your attendance record not matter to you?
Do not ignore me when I'm talking!
Some girl named Hori called, asking about you.
Said she used the home phone because your cell's off.
I'm going to go out on a limb here and guess there's something you want.
You have a rotten history of never admitting when your heart is set on something.
And why you do this is beyond me.
Listen, Yuki.
It's okay to want things.
You shouldn't feel embarrassed.
What's not okay is wallowing in self-pity because you keep letting the things you want pass you by.
Don't let it go if you're just going to complain about it afterward.
Why can't I have a pretty new hair clip that's like the kind she has?
Because when I asked you in the store, you told me you were fine without one.
Here.
Take it.
If there's something you really want, then just say so.
It's an old bad habit I wish you'd break.
This would go a lot better with those cookies you used to bake.
The last batch you did actually turned out pretty well.
Especially the white ones.
Reminded me of you.
Because they look like snow.
Yuki does mean snow.
Here, why?
Like my name.
The poor guy.
Tuesday.
You
Yeah, you're back
About time, right? Yeah, she looks happy
Like dad come on hoodie. Oh
I should mention before I forget did you get my message about the changes to the test? Yeah
I love seeing a squirm though. I squirm regardless because I'm essentially crap at every single subject
Ishikawa
Can we talk
Sure
I guess we could only pretend for so long
Time to wake up from this dream
It's even colder up here than it was on the ground. I'm in a skirt
So can we please make this fast and I gotta give Hori back her notebook before next class
read them
Your text? Yeah, didn't reply, but I'm caught up
Kono told me she liked me
And then she told me that she didn't need me to give her a response
Huh?
Wait
She did mm-hmm
It's because she bought into that rumor about us dating and thinks that I'm taking she confessed anyway to get it off her chest
So wait why not set her straight? Why didn't you tell her was all pretend?
Yes, I don't really know why yeah, I was a misunderstanding
There was no need to explain because I mean I made you a promise that I would play along
Okay, let's say you hadn't made me that promise. How do you think you would have responded to her then?
Please I'm not stupid enough to think we're on par. There's no way. I
May not be good for her, but one day she'll find someone who's up on her level
Ah
You see
Suppose that means no more sakura cookies
Bet you're bummed about that
No kidding
I'm shocked
He's so kind and she's so kind that I thought for sure she'd be the type of girl he'd go for
You were mother cookie supplier for a while. You made them nice and burnt
Shut your face. Don't burn them anymore
I'm so unfair
Kona went to the trouble of baking him cookies every day
She worked up the courage to talk to him and then found even more courage to confess
Despite knowing she'd be rejected
The only thing I ever do is run away
I'd be lying if I said I wasn't relieved the two of them won't be dating anytime soon
Though the thought of me being in the same boat of him not reciprocating my feelings
Makes me scared to breathe
But I'll endure it
Because I want to be the one at his side
Doubt I could be more selfish if I tried
If she's warm and sweet cherry blossoms
And I'm gross muddy bone-chilling snow just like my name suggests
I can see your breath looks cool. I
Heard today's gonna be the coldest day of the year
If mother nature's gonna force us to freeze our butts off, the least she can do is make it snow
Maybe compensate for last year. I'm kind of looking forward to a flurry or two
You're the only person I know who feels that way
You think so? Snow's pretty though
Only when it's freshly fallen
Shoveling it's a pain and there's a good chance you'll slip and fall not pretty
Yeah, you're more to a death have plenty of spills
Exactly and don't get me started on the gross dirty snow that sticks around way too long. Nobody likes that
People want it to melt to feel the warmth of spring
The snow doesn't melt just because it's a different season
Huh?
It melts when it wants to so if it decides it's a good day to go and that's all she wrote
No matter how badly everyone wants another day with it the snow makes the choice to melt away
It calls its own shots
You got that?
It gets warmer in the spring is what I meant
Let me get this straight you think that the snow melts because the sakura blossoms ask
Are we talking about the weather or something else?
Sounds like you need to go back to first grade science
Hey, I'm all right at science
I can't believe how serious he was throughout that entire spiel
I'm glad he said it though
Really glad
Are you trying to break a world record for being stupid or what?
You just don't want me to take your title
There, got your first real smile today
How do you know it's my first?
I just do
Hey, let's get out of this cold
Remind me again whose bright idea was to talk on the roof
Yeah, yeah
Your hands warm
You've got me hoping we get some snow too
The pure and pretty kind
What? You think sakura has a boyfriend now?
Wow, really?
Yeah, maybe it's just me but she seems to have a little more pep in her step
Doesn't she?
You're so wrong
Bye, Remy's off to tutoring
Uh, uh, huh
Despite the tells, she doesn't think sakura is the slightest bit happier?
Or maybe she was referring to my boyfriend hypothesis, is that it?
Sengoku?
I hope you haven't been demoted
Oh, the eraser bits on the floor were bothering me
First year should do that, not student body presidents
I mean, honestly
She's definitely in better spirits
Almost like a weight's been lifted off her shoulders
Plus, you should open the window if you're going to clean
Where's Remy?
She had tutoring today
She's our dependable window opener, as you know
It's been a while since I had to do it, so I guess I forgot
Um, I don't mean to pry, but did something happen to you recently?
You seem much more chipper, so I'd like to believe it was something good
Though, now I'm starting to suspect that may not be the case
Or maybe it's nothing at all
Sorry, I'm overanalyzing this way too much
Is it Sakura?
Oh, I should probably head home
I'm sorry, I can't help you clean
Hold on, wait
Please, don't leave like this
Please
Just take a breath and then tell me what happened
Nothing happened, Sengoku
I got my heart broken, that's all
I didn't even get a response
No big deal
Well, then he's a moron
Straight up stupid
In fact, I don't want someone so dumb to be affiliated with our school
This jerk should be expelled
Chimney?
Hey!
That was the first time I ever saw a classmate break down into uncontrollable tears.
And since nobody's in the wrong, it only hurts more.
Wow, it started snowing.
It started snowing.
Oh